[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of criminal does Tom Cruise portray in the 2004 crime thriller movie Collateral?", "correct_answer": "Assassin", "incorrect_answers": ["Rapist", "Burglar", "Abductor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these Star Wars characters is the odd one out?", "correct_answer": "Senator Bail Organa", "incorrect_answers": ["Chancellor Palpatine", "Darth Sidious", "The Emperor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The sign comes second.  Its personality is descibed as steady and supportive..", "correct_answer": "Ox", "incorrect_answers": ["Horse", "Snake", "Goat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress who had a small role in this film as Bianca Torres girlfriend (Debra Feuer),  later went on to fame in a supporting television series role?", "correct_answer": "Jane Leeves, Frazier", "incorrect_answers": ["Jenna Elfman, Dharma and Greg", "Jennifer Garner, Alias", "Fran Drescher, The Nanny"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This hairless cat breed originated in Russia.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Don Sphynx", "Donskoy", "Don Hairless"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which 2004 movie starring Don Cheadle, was about the hotelier Paul Rusesabagina?", "correct_answer": "Hotel Rwanda", "incorrect_answers": ["Schindlers List", "Nigerian Nights", "H\u00f4tel des Mille Collines"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This abstract strategy board game is the national game of Ghana. The board has two straight rows of six pits or cavities, called houses.", "correct_answer": "Oware", "incorrect_answers": ["Checkers", "Backgammon", "Chess"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to some medieval texts, the name of Norway originated from the name of which of the following?", "correct_answer": "The name of a king", "incorrect_answers": ["A mountain", "The name of a river", "An animal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If I am a superficial muscle of the human body having two prominent bellies, then where am I located?", "correct_answer": "Leg", "incorrect_answers": ["Hip", "Head", "Arm"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many of the Wolverines actually live through the end of the movie Red dawn?", "correct_answer": "2", "incorrect_answers": ["3", "0", "1"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This war film won several Academy Awards and was written and directed by Oliver Stone.", "correct_answer": "Platoon", "incorrect_answers": ["Full Metal Jacket", "Born on the Fourth of July", "Good Morning, Vietnam"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When you take a shower or bath for a long time, the skin on your fingertips shrivels.  This happens because your body does this.", "correct_answer": "Absorbs water in the hypotonic solution", "incorrect_answers": ["Loses water in the hypotonic solution", "Loses water in the hypertonic solution", "Absorbs water in the hypertonic solution"]}]